[{"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395b7", "question": "In The Simpsons episode, \"Bart Gets an 'F',\" what sickness does Lisa have?", "answer": "Mumps", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8a2", "question": "Which element of the periodic table is named after the formulator of the periodic table?", "answer": "Mendelevium", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c438", "question": "A group of lions is called a what?", "answer": "Pride", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133905b", "question": "Once married to Ted Hughes, which American poet committed suicide in 1963?", "answer": "Sylvia Plath", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b481", "question": "What year did the Franco-Prussian War begin?", "answer": "1870", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fd81fdfd0de9af39e9d469a", "question": "What year did Amazon.com make its first sale?", "answer": "1995", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c43f", "question": "What mammal's most common species is the bottlenose?", "answer": "Dolphin's", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133950f", "question": "Who voiced the character Atta in the movie \"A Bug's Life\"?", "answer": "Julia Louis Dreyfuss", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7fe", "question": "What are the two landlocked countries in South America?", "answer": "Bolivia and Paraguay", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58f16ae3f7c52aae91cc07e2", "question": "What sort of food are \"rollmops\"?", "answer": "Fish", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd00", "question": "What South African antelope lent its name to a brand of athletic shoe?", "answer": "The rhebok", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e7a", "question": "During what war was the novel \"M*A*S*H\" set?", "answer": "Korean War", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59523c9d736d4be723796b39", "question": "What are Canada\u2019s two official sports?", "answer": "Ice hockey and lacrosse", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7b5", "question": "What do the letters X.O. stand for on a bottle of cognac?", "answer": "Extra Old", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b963", "question": "How many quires are there in a ream?", "answer": "20", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6f8", "question": "What Olympic field event's two main styles are the glide and the spin?", "answer": "Shot put's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fecc10cec223966ae8f8864", "question": "In the 2007 Superbowl, a player used what piece of equipment to make a catch?", "answer": "Helmet", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fef96966ce05a3942286e9e", "question": "In \"Scooby-Doo,\" what was Shaggy's real name?", "answer": "Norville Rogers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a40e", "question": "The Thousand Islands are located in what body of water?", "answer": "St. Lawrence River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c71d", "question": "What is a tanager?", "answer": "A bird", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339286", "question": "Who is the only player in season 14 of the TV show \"Big Brother\" to be in the house but not have a key?", "answer": "Jodi", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe93cd86bd93ce3a4e5f6ad", "question": "What scientist discovered X-rays?", "answer": "Wilhelm R\u00f6ntgen", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398d6", "question": "Where did Fonzie, Richie, Potsie and Ralph go to drink sodas and play the jukebox?", "answer": "Arnold's Drive-In", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba17", "question": "The Houston Comets won what league's first ever championship title?", "answer": "Women's National Basketball Association", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe8f81f01dd7bf43be5e840", "question": "Achluophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Darkness", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b43a", "question": "When was Albert Einstein born?", "answer": "1879", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6015e8cdfe83fe1f2a824bdf", "question": "Which rebellious leader of the Catuvellauni tribe was caught and taken to Rome in AD 50, then pardoned by Emperor Claudius?", "answer": "Caractacus", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113389e5", "question": "What game was invented when Winnie-the-Pooh accidentally dropped a fir cone off a bridge?", "answer": "Poohsticks", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a1a", "question": "What female band had hits in the 1980\u2019s with the songs \"Cruel Summer\" and \"Venus\"?", "answer": "Bananarama", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa49", "question": "Which ocean is The Gulf Stream\u00a0in?", "answer": "The Atlantic\u00a0", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad4f", "question": "How many openings were there in the Berlin Wall?", "answer": "Two", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac5e", "question": "Who is said to have been presented to Julius Caesar in a carpet?", "answer": "Cleopatra", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5c90d3ff52800b05cac20f1a", "question": "What is the real name of the DC character Deathstroke?", "answer": "Slade Wilson", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ffb60865dad637d903c882a", "question": "Off what country are the islands of Islay, Mull, and St. Kilda located?", "answer": "Scotland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ffa57fbc73aa70ea0b70b37", "question": "Which U.S. state features the Italian phrase \"Fatti maschii, parole femine\" as its state motto?", "answer": "Maryland  (The motto translates as \u201cManly deeds, womanly words.\u201d\u00a0 The state uses\u00a0\"Strong deeds, gentle words\".)", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fc6", "question": "Who rode Rocinante?", "answer": "Don Quixote", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133957e", "question": "What game was played for money by the Vietnamese in \"The Deer Hunter\" movie?", "answer": "Russian Roulette", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a85", "question": "What were the names of Ann Romano's two daughters on \"One Day at a Time\"?", "answer": "Barbara and Julie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b523", "question": "What is the main difference between a supercharger and a turbocharger?", "answer": "Superchargers are usually belt driven, while turbochargers gas driven.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b68f", "question": "Notch, peak, and shank are different types of what?", "answer": "Lapels", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5b35891a5db0d66a186cb548", "question": "What word is used to identify the residents of Burkina Faso?", "answer": "Burkinabe", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8f3", "question": "What range contains the world's highest mountains not located in Asia?", "answer": "The Andes", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2a6", "question": "How many grams is 1 Troy Ounce?", "answer": "31.1 grams", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58b8d6f32b42d4a3561a9f09", "question": "What country is Dinish Island a part of?", "answer": "Ireland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b802", "question": "What is the point value of the letter Q in the standard game of Scrabble?", "answer": "10", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5bb35b4f2627b8fe95581beb", "question": "In ABC's \"Once Upon a Time\" what character was played by Colin O' Donoghue?", "answer": "Captain Hook", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0e5", "question": "Japan signed the term of surrender for WWII aboard which US battleship?", "answer": "USS Missouri", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e86", "question": "What species are mingled to produce a Centaur?", "answer": "Human and horse", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59ded115ea2747c8aff16d2f", "question": "What is Thalassophobia the fear of?", "answer": "The Sea or sea travel", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fefc1ed6ce05a3942286f18", "question": "What country is the setting for the film \"The Deep\"?", "answer": "Bermuda", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fbe", "question": "What instrument did bandleader Glenn Miller play?", "answer": "Trombone", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b584", "question": "What is the name for Argentinean cowboys?", "answer": "Gauchos", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58dba395874c93a3298b213d", "question": "Who was nicknamed La Pucelle d'Orl\u00e9ans?", "answer": "Joan of Arc", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3f0", "question": "In which hemisphere is the Tropic of Cancer located?", "answer": "Northern", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd6a47b6c0f9723ab15cb54", "question": "Who was USA' first female governor?", "answer": "Nellie Tayloe Ross", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fefbfda6ce05a3942286f06", "question": "Who recorded the song \"Tango in the Night\"?", "answer": "Fleetwood Mac", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea3fa7ff048f679a45ab61", "question": "How many stomachs does a llama have?", "answer": "Three", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a990", "question": "What city named its airport after Galileo Galilei?", "answer": "Pisa", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0eb", "question": "Christopher Cockerell is best known for invented what?", "answer": "The hovercraft", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea3e9eff048f679a45ab5c", "question": "High blood pressure is also known as what?", "answer": "Hypertension", "category": "science"}, {"id": "601b4abb49076251badbeabb", "question": "Where is the oldest African-American theater located in the U.S.?", "answer": "Cleveland, Ohio -- Karamu House opened to the public in 1915. The name is Swahili, meaning \"a place of joyful gathering\".", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7d8", "question": "Which university did Bill Gates drop out of in the 1970s to start Microsoft?", "answer": "Harvard", "category": "general"}, {"id": "597ddd3077980686f722d17c", "question": "When was the first permanent photograph taken?", "answer": "1826", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7cd", "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the \"Green Mountain State\"?", "answer": "Vermont", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a27f", "question": "Vinnie Jones was associated with which sport?", "answer": "Soccer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b00", "question": "Which character killed Fyodor Karamazov?", "answer": "Smerdyakov", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2fa", "question": "Who played the role of Grant in the 1966 film \"Fantastic Voyage\"?", "answer": "Stephen Boyd", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ea0", "question": "What future star's neck is broken by Bruce Lee in the cave fight in \"Enter the Dragon\"?", "answer": "Jackie Chan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ad6", "question": "Who wrote King George V Christmas speech that was broadcast in 1932?", "answer": "Rudyard Kipling", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea37f3ff048f679a45ab1e", "question": "What is it called when you make light change direction by passing it through a lens?", "answer": "Refraction", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5e1", "question": "What name is given to the study of the behavior and flow of air around objects?", "answer": "Aerodynamics", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c02c", "question": "What does Amoco stand for?", "answer": "American Oil Company", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339640", "question": "Oswald Cobblepot is better known as who?", "answer": "The Penguin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a995", "question": "In what country would you find the active volcano \"Etna\"?", "answer": "Italy", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cae8", "question": "What is the study of soils in their natural environment called?", "answer": "Pedology", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe9f4ddff048f679a45aacc", "question": "Mageirocophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Cooking", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d08", "question": "What mythological figure flew too close to the sun, and fell into the sea and drown when the sun melted the wax on his wings?", "answer": "Icarus", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e3a", "question": "What children's classic first chapter is titled \"Mrs. Rachel Lynde Is Surprised\"?", "answer": "Anne of Green Gables", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7b8", "question": "What is measured in Millibars?", "answer": "Pressure", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f90", "question": "What actress earned an Oscar nomination for her first screen appearance in \"The Heart is a Lonely Hunter\"?", "answer": "Sandra Locke", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b285", "question": "What position was first held by Steve Allen?", "answer": "Tonight Show host", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59ca3d5444f0f6af5b066639", "question": "Who had a hit with the song \"Don't Pay The Ferryman\"?", "answer": "Chris de Burgh", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59a7f51a6f5f79087132fb3d", "question": "What do British people call zucchini?", "answer": "Courgette", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58f166adf7c52aae91cc07b0", "question": "Of what do earthworms have five?", "answer": "Blood vessels", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6015dfddfe83fe1f2a824b82", "question": "When was the first fax machine invented?", "answer": "1840s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e4f", "question": "What athlete had a part in the movie \"Amazing Grace and Chuck\"?", "answer": "Alex English", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ba5", "question": "What sitcom was the #1 rated TV show for five straight seasons during the 1970's?", "answer": "All in the Family", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bae1", "question": "In what country was the International Red Cross founded?", "answer": "Switzerland", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5954e9c48e82ccaf3b9a67bd", "question": "What food group is a cucumber technically in?", "answer": "Fruits", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339aad", "question": "What popular children\u2019s book did Forrest Gump keep in his briefcase?", "answer": "Curious George", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fc2f050cee580c7f8fd1e4b", "question": "Who was Truman Capote's research assistant for his book \"In Cold Blood\"?", "answer": "Harper Lee", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b756", "question": "What team did basketball star Larry Bird play 13 seasons for?", "answer": "Boston Celtics", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5febaf0d7e83c707845b20fa", "question": "What is the most venomous fish in the world?", "answer": "Reef stonefish", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fecdcfaec223966ae8f88fb", "question": "In the film \"Goodfellas\", what airline is robbed?", "answer": "Lufthansa", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59774433284458f1d785442e", "question": "The original name of New York City was what?", "answer": "New Amsterdam", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca4e", "question": "What is Frank Whittle credited with inventing?", "answer": "Turbojet engine", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe775edeec85e375820b313", "question": "How many states does Mexico have?", "answer": "31", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c649", "question": "Where do bumblebees normally build their nests?", "answer": "Underground", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5f30576d5aa2bc17b61b2ad0", "question": "What is the historical term, \"Dipsomania\" another name for what modern day condition?", "answer": "Alcholism", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b672", "question": "Where on a ship would you find the crow's nest?", "answer": "On the tallest mast", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe6a91420565ad31a57c7fc", "question": "What Dallas nightclub did Oswald murderer Jack Ruby own?", "answer": "The Carousel Club", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5904a0a4cf93664eb10486b9", "question": "What year was the Norwegian non-profit organization, \"Norse Federation\" founded?", "answer": "1907", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ddd", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"pundit\"?", "answer": "Hindi", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398c6", "question": "Singer Stefani Joanne Angelina Germanotta is better known by what stage name?", "answer": "Lady Gaga", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5cefc077948005ec986edcdb", "question": "Who is the second member of the group LOONA to debut? ", "answer": "Hyunjin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5922049aa4edfd43a087ade6", "question": "Butter bean is another name for which type of bean?", "answer": "Lima", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f18", "question": "What author created Earthsea?", "answer": "Ursula K. Le Guin", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a590", "question": "What U.S. state is proud to call itself \"the Beaver State\"?", "answer": "Oregon", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ab99d1f21a8909e5c332d3e", "question": "What was Harold Lloyd Jenkins' stage name?", "answer": "Conway Twitty", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3e6", "question": "What was the first NASA program to land an object on Mars that sent information back to Earth?", "answer": "Viking", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58ab1832baab681b09292187", "question": "Which racing team introduced a six-wheeled race car in 1974 and began racing it in 1976?", "answer": "Tyrrell Racing", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133930f", "question": "In \"The Big Lebowski\", what did Jeffrey Lebowski want replaced after it was urinated on?", "answer": "His rug", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac3f", "question": "What Roman god is January named for?", "answer": "Janus", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a464", "question": "Mount Rushmore is located near which town in South Dakota?", "answer": "Keystone", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5febbc737e83c707845b214c", "question": "Which band's debut album was entitled \"Appetite for Destruction\"?", "answer": "Guns N' Roses'", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea32aeff048f679a45aae9", "question": "How often do your taste buds regenerate on average?", "answer": "Every ten days", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c697", "question": "In the human body, what is produced by the Islets of Langerhans?", "answer": "Insulin", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd79", "question": "What open-faced Italian omelette is, despite its name, more often baked than fried?", "answer": "Frittata", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5bb", "question": "What is the common term for epinephrine?", "answer": "Adrenalin", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c935", "question": "What is an Otoscope used to look at?", "answer": "The Ear", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b267", "question": "What empress gave John Paul Jones a navy job after his American military career ended?", "answer": "Catherine the Great", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133978a", "question": "What is the name of the bar in the TV show Family Guy that is frequently visited by Peter Griffin and his friends?", "answer": "The Drunken Clam", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133945a", "question": "Who does Eddie Murphy trade places with in the 1983 movie \"Trading Places\"?", "answer": "Dan Aykroyd", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59cdb1ef65ff7d326b622a6e", "question": "Animals and plants which produce light are said to be what?", "answer": "Bioluminescent", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c02", "question": "Tony Pastor is credited with popularizing what form of theater in the early 1880s?", "answer": "Vaudeville", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff6685052a821ff76ae8b03", "question": "Around what sea did Jesus call His first apostles?", "answer": "Christ first saw Peter and Andrew close to the Sea of Galilee. He beseeched them to follow Him.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397cd", "question": "Who played Sofia in the movie \"The Color Purple\"?", "answer": "Oprah Winfrey", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fef61f16ce05a3942286e59", "question": "What does the \"MS\" reference in \"MSNBC\"?", "answer": "Microsoft", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394c5", "question": "What was the family name of the aliens on the TV show \"3rd Rock from the Sun\"?", "answer": "The Solomons", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a18d", "question": "What is the name of the oscar winning actor who is the spokesperson for Farmer's Insurance?", "answer": "J.K. Simmons", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ffb66ca5dad637d903c8839", "question": "What major city elected Sadiq Khan, its first mayor from an ethnic minority, in 2016?", "answer": "Greater London, England", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339664", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", Marge decided to sell what snack food?", "answer": "Pretzels", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b13f", "question": "How many months did it take the Mayflower to cross the Atlantic Ocean?", "answer": "2", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fec8be1ec223966ae8f8844", "question": "Which television series revolves around a concierge doctor making house calls in the Hamptons?", "answer": "\"Royal Pains\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "596dfe159616e6c6d4eba4fb", "question": "What island does the Statue of Liberty stand on?", "answer": "Liberty Island", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b2a", "question": "What 1973 horror movie features the characters Father Merrin and Father Karras?", "answer": "The Exorcist", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b60", "question": "What is the highest female voice in a choir?", "answer": "Soprano", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fec8591ec223966ae8f8807", "question": "Who directed both \"Frankenstein\" and \"The Invisible Man\"?", "answer": "James Whale", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338aa7", "question": "What Saturday Evening Post artist was known for his whimsical pictures of Santa Claus?", "answer": "Norman Rockwell", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "601b4bff49076251badbeacb", "question": "Which U.S. President had the most children?", "answer": "John Tyler -- The 10th president had 16 children \u2014 15 with his two wives and one born out of wedlock.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fd66cfea5bfecdd737e0899", "question": "Where is the original London Bridge structure today?", "answer": "Arizona", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392fd", "question": "In the movie \"The Karate Kid\", what is the name of Daniel's master?", "answer": "Mr. Miyagi", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea7815ff048f679a45abd3", "question": "What is the tallest type of horse?", "answer": "Shire", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113389cd", "question": "What literary character is adopted by Messua and her husband who believe him to be their long-lost sibling?", "answer": "Mowgli", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfb7", "question": "Which building material gets its name from Arabic for \"brick\"?", "answer": "Adobe", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133beb1", "question": "What title was given to Nanak, the founder of Sikhism?", "answer": "Guru", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58b8ce8d94b094db915830a8", "question": "What did the letters \u201cC\u201d and \u201cN\u201d originally stand for in Toronto\u2019s CN Tower", "answer": "Canadian National", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58f16abaf7c52aae91cc07e0", "question": "What is Australia's highest mainland mountain?", "answer": "Mount Kosciuszko", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339048", "question": "Which Tennesee Williams play is about a Italian-American woman?", "answer": "The Rose Tattoo", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339428", "question": "Who played Hank's love interest in the 2001 movie \"Monster's Ball\"?", "answer": "Halle Berry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339325", "question": "In the movie \"Monsters Inc.\", what are the monsters most scared of?", "answer": "Children", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5990f8a6fa5fdd6dd25324ef", "question": "Which city is home to Colman's mustard?", "answer": "Norwich", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "592eaccaf83302ff91e46473", "question": "What part of a wine bottle is the punt?", "answer": "The indentation in the base", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca39", "question": "Which element appears fifth on the periodic table?", "answer": "Boron", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c02f", "question": "What type of food is Fontina?", "answer": "Cheese", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae96", "question": "The 16th Constitutional Amendment, enacted in 1913 allowed the US federal government to do what?", "answer": "Tax personal income", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca79", "question": "What is the Latin word for the beech tree?", "answer": "Fagus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399c5", "question": "What was Mr. Seaver's first name on the TV show \"Growing Pains\"?", "answer": "Jason", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c677", "question": "What inventor was known as the \"Wizard of Menlo Park\"?", "answer": "Thomas Edison", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a59e", "question": "In what mountains is Camp David?", "answer": "Appalachian Mountains", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113389f5", "question": "Which Paul McCartney and Wings album includes \"Picasso's Last Words\"?", "answer": "Band on the Run", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afe3", "question": "During what war did Nathan Hale become a national hero?", "answer": "American Revolution", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6015ffb5fe83fe1f2a824c4f", "question": "The term \"bonfire\" originated from which two Halloween related words?", "answer": "Bone and fire -- Bonfire is associated with ancient Celts where the bones of animals were burnt in order to fend off bad spirits.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "593c4b07b8198b9a2b077960", "question": "Who starred opposite Jack Nicholson in the film \"As Good as It Gets\"?", "answer": "Helen Hunt", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e2f", "question": "Who is Sean Astin's mother?", "answer": "Patty Duke", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b013", "question": "Who was \"Time\" magazine's first \"person of the year\"?", "answer": "Charles Lindburgh", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392d1", "question": "What actress portrayed the title character in the 1965 big-screen Western \"Cat Ballou\"?", "answer": "Jane Fonda", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4b7", "question": "What is divided into the duodenum, the jejunum, and the ileum?", "answer": "The small intestine", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aed9", "question": "How many times did Mary Queen of Scots get married?", "answer": "Three Times", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59e80272de59ea584496fe96", "question": "What river is Liverpool situated on?", "answer": "Mersey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5921fcf3a4edfd43a087adc6", "question": "What number is represented by \"D\" in Roman numerals?", "answer": "500", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b077", "question": "What was the last name of Civil Rights activist Malcolm X?", "answer": "Little", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9e7", "question": "Where is the Popliteal Fossa located?", "answer": "Back of the knee", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd7e", "question": "According to the Bible, who died at the ripe old age of 930?", "answer": "Adam", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdb3", "question": "What Big US East school took the cryptic name for its sports teams from the Greek word for \"what\"?", "answer": "Georgetown", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339658", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", why did Bart and Homer have to work at the carnival?", "answer": "Bart wrecked Hitler's car", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba62", "question": "What was the nickname of the 1960\u2019s model born Leslie Hornby?", "answer": "Twiggy", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a4d97cb08b8581f80b092ab", "question": "Which popular US actress died on January 25, 2017, at the age of 80?", "answer": "Mary Tyler Moore", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58b0ea41964118b2bb3809d0", "question": "What year did the \"ILOVEYOU\" virus began infecting computers worldwide?", "answer": "2000", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5901da79709c1c34536e6eaf", "question": "In ice hockey, how many players for each team are allowed on the ice at the same time?", "answer": "Six", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fecc1e6ec223966ae8f886f", "question": "Who allegedly wrote the song \"Golden Years\" for Elvis Presley but ended up recording it himself?", "answer": "David Bowie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c612", "question": "On a map, the vertical lines are called what?", "answer": "Longitude", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae33", "question": "When did the War of 1812 actually begin?", "answer": "1812", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fde4e82c6c6b019850c9a84", "question": "November 11, 1921 marked the first anonymous burial at what famous U.S. cemetery?", "answer": "Arlington National Cemetery", "category": "history"}, {"id": "592eaec8f83302ff91e4648c", "question": "Mark David Chapman became famous for what in 1980?", "answer": "Shooting John Lennon", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb28", "question": "In baseball score-keeping, what number represents the third baseman's position?", "answer": "5", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7a9", "question": "How many US state capital cities lie on the Mississippi River?", "answer": "Two - Baton Rouge and St. Paul", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c85c", "question": "The scientist Bernard Vonnegut, brother of famed author Kurt Vonnegut, discovered what commercial use for silver iodide?", "answer": "Rainmaking", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338dcd", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"smorgasbord\"?", "answer": "Swedish", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aaed", "question": "Dodoma is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Tanzania", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fea7dabff048f679a45abfb", "question": "Algophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Pain", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5afad941430e050a5df0d114", "question": "According to most sources, where is the world\u2019s tallest unclimbed unclimable mountain?", "answer": "Bhutan/China", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba48", "question": "What US city hosts the world's largest hot air balloon festival?", "answer": "Albuquerque", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a828", "question": "In which US city is the United States Naval Academy located?", "answer": "Annapolis, Maryland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f7f", "question": "What was Bo Donaldson's backing band?", "answer": "The Heywoods", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1d7", "question": "What is added to cognac to make a Stinger cocktail?", "answer": "White creme de menthe", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe65e461f3c0ead6880d628", "question": "What biblical figure had a slave named Onesimus?", "answer": "Philemon", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c168", "question": "What sport is Edson Arantes do Nascimento associated with?", "answer": "Soccer", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5b1745c3bb2d29f81593b703", "question": "In which capital city was the crime fighting organisation \"Interpol\" founded?", "answer": "Vienna", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338983", "question": "Who is the tomboy main character in the book \"Little Women\"?", "answer": "Josephine (Jo) March", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fd66959a5bfecdd737e087a", "question": "Who was the last king of Troy in Greek mythology?", "answer": "Priam", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133991e", "question": "What is the name of the singer known by her stage name \"Fergie\"?", "answer": "Stacy Ferguson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391ad", "question": "Who recorded the international hit single \"Poker Face\" in 2008?", "answer": "Lady Gaga", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1d6", "question": "What two ingredients are used to make the standard Stinger cocktail?", "answer": "Cognac and white creme de menthe", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd87", "question": "What type of animal is the Japanese monster, Kumonga?", "answer": "Spider", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59ca3c2944f0f6af5b06662d", "question": "How does Wonder Woman control her invisible airplane?", "answer": "Mental powers", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a65c", "question": "The port city of Sandusky is located in which state?", "answer": "Ohio", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59049d3bcf93664eb10486ac", "question": "Which famous pop star considers the number 13 to be her lucky number?", "answer": "Taylor Swift", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4aa", "question": "Which country were the 1948 Summer Olympic Games held in?", "answer": "United Kingdom", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b790", "question": "What is the plastic piece at the end of a shoelace called?", "answer": "Aglet", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fed", "question": "What is the fear, or hatred of books called?", "answer": "Bibliophobia", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133983f", "question": "Who was the first winner of the TV show \"America's Next Top Model\"?", "answer": "Adrianne Curry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b00e", "question": "What was Lyndon B. Johnson's middle name?", "answer": "Baines", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b3589855db0d66a186cb54c", "question": "The Republic of Benin shares a border with which other African country to the east?", "answer": "Nigeria", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b08c", "question": "What was the nickname of American frontiersman Christopher Houston Carson?", "answer": "Kit", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ad2", "question": "Mila Kunis played what role on \"That '70s Show\"?", "answer": "Jackie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b323331bf195a31e15d7398", "question": "What is the capital of Botswana?", "answer": "Gaborone", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6fa", "question": "What river flows through the city of Little Rock?", "answer": "Arkansas River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4d3", "question": "On what holiday did Harry Houdini die in 1926?", "answer": "Halloween", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bdc", "question": "In which city is A Midsummer Nights Dream set?", "answer": "Athens", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392a5", "question": "What novel-inspired role did Anthony Hopkins say he based partly on HAL 9000, the Space Odyssey computer?", "answer": "Hannibal Lecter", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca7b", "question": "Who was the first dog in space?", "answer": "Laika", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd64", "question": "In what US state are submarine sandwiches traditionally called \"po' boys\"?", "answer": "Louisiana", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5937ee8a08d98002fdd633d5", "question": "This is the strongest poker hand you can get?", "answer": "Royal Flush", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea48caff048f679a45abb4", "question": "What snake has the longest fangs?", "answer": "Gaboon Viper", "category": "science"}, {"id": "594a63662ebb971c1417fb99", "question": "Who performed the 1977 song \"Let's All Chant\"?", "answer": "The Michael Zager Band", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdaa", "question": "Nepetalactone is the active ingredient in what pet product?", "answer": "Catnip", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a54", "question": "What university presents the annual Pulitzer Prize journalism awards?", "answer": "Colombia", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ab3", "question": "What were Donner and Blitzen's names in the 1823 publication of, A Visit from St. Nicholas", "answer": "Dunder and Blixen", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a14f", "question": "What city do Batman and Robin patrol?", "answer": "Gotham City", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600787ce0eee65b76b9f265d", "question": "According to Greek mythology who was the first woman on earth?", "answer": "Pandora", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c585", "question": "The material nylon is named after which 2 cities?", "answer": "New York and London", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b309", "question": "Who was found in a \"spider hole\" on December 13, 2003?", "answer": "Saddam Hussein", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c363", "question": "What part of the body does an orthopedic doctor treat?", "answer": "Bones", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a65e", "question": "Which US state is home to the Steamboat Geyser?", "answer": "Wyoming", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b006", "question": "What war gave the US its freedom from Britain?", "answer": "American Revolution", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe65797ae7e414034b5aede", "question": "Facebook co-founder Sean Parker was also the co-founder of which company?", "answer": "Napster", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9aa", "question": "What mountain is the tallest point in Australia?", "answer": "Kosciusko", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59071da73745b36be73039db", "question": "Who became the first American in space in 1961?", "answer": "Alan Shepard", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58b8d5a72b42d4a3561a9f04", "question": "In the comic book series \"Strangers in Paradise\", when is Katchoo\u2019s birthday?", "answer": "November 19", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff0b3a2e662d71a53650fe0", "question": "Johann Sebastian Bach wrote a comic opera about which beverage?", "answer": "Coffee", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f84", "question": "What is the name of the son of the witch Sycorax?", "answer": "Caliban in The Tempest", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6cc", "question": "What US city and its surroundings is the basis for a standard US Monopoly board?", "answer": "Atlantic City", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5937ec9d08d98002fdd633bd", "question": "Equatorial Guinea gained independence from which country in 1968?", "answer": "Spain", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339821", "question": "Who played Dolly Levi in the film adaptation of \"Hello Dolly\"?", "answer": "Barbra Streisand", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5f4", "question": "Which US state is known as the \u201cLand of Enchantment\u201d?", "answer": "New Mexico", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fef669f6ce05a3942286e7a", "question": "How many of the original three Star Wars films did George Lucas direct?", "answer": "One", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c77", "question": "What year was Indiana Jones first introduced to the public?", "answer": "1981", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339235", "question": "Who played little Gertie in the movie \"E.T.: The Extra-Terrestrial\"?", "answer": "Drew Barrymore", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4b2", "question": "When did the Jallianwahla Bagh massacre take place?", "answer": "April 13, 1919", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be82", "question": "What raconteur and Topkapi star joked that he wanted his tombstone to read \"Keep off the grass\"?", "answer": "Peter Ustinov", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c5c", "question": "What Californian city was George Lucas born in?", "answer": "Modesto", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396cb", "question": "Who played the role of Dr. Frasier Crane in the TV show \"Frasier\"?", "answer": "Kelsey Grammer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b047", "question": "The ocean liner RMS Carpathia played a role in what historical event?", "answer": "Sinking of the Titanic", "category": "history"}, {"id": "60173e4644491cbd7c5a17af", "question": "What two U.S. Presidents\u2019 grandson and daughter married each other?", "answer": "Eisenhower & Nixon -- President Nixon's daughter, Julie, married President Eisenhower's grandson, Dwight David Eisenhower, II.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fec849eec223966ae8f8800", "question": "Sozin's comet is an astrological event that occurs in which television series?", "answer": "\"Avatar: the Last Airbender\"", "category": "entertainment"}]